viatrading.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Via Trading Corporation

## Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of Via Trading Corporation.

Our physical and mailing address is:

Via Trading Corporation2520 Industry WayLynwood, CA, 90262 

We can be reached via e-mail at [sales@viatrading.com](mailto:sales@viatrading.com) or by telephone at **877-202-3616** (+323-214-8914 from overseas).

Our Web Server automatically recognizes any visitor’s IP address and access type which helps us gather broad demographic information. No personal information is captured by our server unless you provide it to us when registering on our site.

Our server should only collect the domain name/IP address of our visitors, but does not collect email addresses. Any personal information we obtain is entered by you when responding to surveys or volunteering your email address and information when registering on our site or mailing list or when you send us an email.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website and to help diagnose potential problems with our server.

Our site uses cookies to record session information and to keep track of your user account. They track information such as what items users add to their shopping carts, and what pages users access or visit. These help us tailor our website to our users’ interests and needs in order to provide more relevant product information.

If you supply us with your e-mail address by registering on our website or joining our mailing list or by sending us an email, you may receive periodic email updates from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by emailing us at [sales@viatrading.com](mailto:sales@viatrading.com) or calling us at **877-202-3616**. You can also opt out of any mailings you receive by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each mailing. Unsubscribing from the list will remove you from our mailing list. Should you wish to receive our mailings again in the future, you will need to join our mailing list once again on [www.viatrading.com](http://www.viatrading.com/ "http://www.viatrading.com").

When emailing or calling us to remove you from our contact list, please be ready to provide us with your full name and address to make sure your name is removed from the list. If you have any questions or require more information about how any of your information is used, please feel free to call or email us anytime.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers when registering online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line or special events, new products and services or promotions Via Trading is sponsoring. If you do not wish to receive such phone calls, please let us know by emailing us at [sales@viatrading.com](mailto:sales@viatrading.com).

When emailing, please provide us with your full name and address so that we may accurately identify you and remove you from our call list.

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Browsing [ViaTrading.com](http://www.viatrading.com/ "http://www.viatrading.com") does not distribute your information to any third party ad server companies.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site and notify you of these changes. We will always provide you with the ability to opt out of any new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you can check our Privacy Policy for any changes, or email us at [sales@viatrading.com](mailto:sales@viatrading.com) with any questions.

Upon request, we can provide site visitors with access to all information we have about them (including proprietary information): Financial information (e.g., credit card account information), unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password), transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number). Consumers can gain access to this information by e-mailing us at the above address.

Contact information and Credit Card information are kept in our physical facility and are not shared with any third parties. Credit Cards are processed physically in-house and do not go through an online third party Credit Card processing company.

Any inaccuracies in a user’s contact information can easily be updated. Please email us at [sales@viatrading.com](mailto:sales@viatrading.com) or call **877-202-3616** if you notice any incorrect information in your account which you would like to see corrected.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you on our site.

If you feel that this site does not follow its stated **Privacy Policy** , you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
